	var quizArray = [{
		"id":"0",
		"question":"Which instrument is used to measure pressure?",
		"choice1":"Saccharimeter",
		"choice2":"Ammeter",
		"choice3":"Manometer",
		"choice4":"Lactometer",
		"correct":"Manometer"
	},
	{
		"id":"1",
		"question":"What does Angstrom measure?",
		"choice1":"Quantity of liquid",
		"choice2":"Length of light waves",
		"choice3":"Length of cables",
		"choice4":"Speed of ships",
		"correct":"Quantity of liquid"
	},
	{
		"id":"2",
		"question":"Light year is related to",
		"choice1":"Energy",
		"choice2":"Speed",
		"choice3":"Distance",
		"choice4":"Intensity",
		"correct":"Distance"
	},
	{
		
		"id":"3",
		"question":"Which of the following instruments is used to measure pressure of gases",
		"choice1":"Barometer",
		"choice2":"Manometer",
		"choice3":"Ammeter",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"Barometer"
	},
	{
		"id":"4",
		"question":"Joule is the unit of?",
		"choice1":"Temperature pressure",
		"choice2":"Energy",
		"choice3":"Heat",
		"choice4":"Cold",
		"correct":"Energy"
	},
	{
		"id":"5",
		"question":"How many Dynes are there in one gram weight?",
		"choice1":"900",
		"choice2":"375",
		"choice3":"981",
		"choice4":"250",
		"correct":"981"
	},
	{
		"id":"6",
		"question":"The unit of current is",
		"choice1":"Ohm",
		"choice2":"Watt",
		"choice3":"Ampere",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"Ampere"
	},
	{
		"id":"7",
		"question":"The unit of energy in MKS system is",
		"choice1":"Volt",
		"choice2":"Erg",
		"choice3":"Ohm",
		"choice4":"Joule",
		"correct":"Joule"
	},
	{
		"id":"8",
		"question":"The intensity of an earthquake is measured with a",
		"choice1":".Barometer",
		"choice2":"Hydrometer",
		"choice3":"Polygraph",
		"choice4":"Seismograph",
		"correct":"Seismograph"
	},
	{
		"id":"9",
		"question":"Centigrade & Fahrenheit scales give same reading at",
		"choice1":"- 400o",
		"choice2":"- 32o",
		"choice3":"- 273o",
		"choice4":"- 100oL",
		"correct":"- 400o"
	},
	{
		"id":"10",
		"question":"Who among the following described protoplasm as the physical basis of life?",
		"choice1":"T. H. Huxley",
		"choice2":"Leeuwenhoek",
		"choice3":"Rudolf Virchow",
		"choice4":"J. C. Bose",
		"correct":"T. H. Huxley"
	},
	{
		"id":"11",
		"question":"The scientist who first discovered that the earth revolves round the sun was",
		"choice1":"Newton",
		"choice2":"Dalton",
		"choice3":"Copernicus",
		"choice4":"Einstein",
		"correct":"Copernicus"
	},
	{
		"id":"12",
		"question":"Alexander Fleming discovered",
		"choice1":"Penicillin",
		"choice2":"X-ray",
		"choice3":"Streptomycin",
		"choice4":"Telephone",
		"correct":"Penicillin"
	},
	{
		"id":"13",
		"question":"Who among following invented the steam engine?",
		"choice1":"Marconi",
		"choice2":"James Watt",
		"choice3":"Thomas Savery",
		"choice4":"Wright Brothers",
		"correct":"James Watt"
	},
	{
		"id":"14",
		"question":"Who invented typewriter?",
		"choice1":"Shockley",
		"choice2":"Pascal",
		"choice3":"Sholes",
		"choice4":"Waterman",
		"correct":"Sholes"
	},
	{
		"id":"15",
		"question":"Who discovered circulation of blood in human body?",
		"choice1":"Edward Jenner ",
		"choice2":"Joseph Lister",
		"choice3":"William Harvey",
		"choice4":"Jonon Esals",
		"correct":"William Harvey"
	},
	{
		"id":"16",
		"question":"The first attempt in printing was made in England by",
		"choice1":"James Arkwright",
		"choice2":"James Watt",
		"choice3":"William Caxton",
		"choice4":"Isaac Newton",
		"correct":"William Caxton"
	},
	{
		"id":"17",
		"question":"Who was the surgeon who pioneered antiseptic surgery in 1865? ",
		"choice1":"Edward Jenner",
		"choice2":"Joseph Lister",
		"choice3":"Henry William",
		"choice4":"John Sleeman",
		"correct":"Joseph Lister"
	},
	{
		"id":"18",
		"question":"The credit of inventing the television goes to",
		"choice1":"Faraday ",
		"choice2":"Baird",
		"choice3":"Edison",
		"choice4":"Marconi",
		"correct":"Baird"
	},
	{
		"id":"19",
		"question":"Philology is the",
		"choice1":"Study of bones",
		"choice2":"Study of muscles",
		"choice3":"Study of architecture",
		"choice4":"Study of languages ",
		"correct":"Study of languages "
	},
	{
		"id":"20",
		"question":"Anatomy is the branch of science which deals with",
		"choice1":"Structure of animals and plants",
		"choice2":"Functioning of body organs",
		"choice3":"Animal behavior",
		"choice4":"Cells and tissues",
		"correct":"Structure of animals and plants"
	},
	{
		"id":"21",
		"question":"Study of earthquakes is known as",
		"choice1":"Ecology",
		"choice2":"Seismology",
		"choice3":"Numismatics",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"Seismology"
	},
	{
		"id":"22",
		"question":"Ecology deals with",
		"choice1":"Birds",
		"choice2":"Cell formation",
		"choice3":"Relation between Organisms and their environment",
		"choice4":"Tissues",
		"correct":"Relation between Organisms and their environment"
	},
	{
		"id":"23",
		"question":"Meteorology is the science of",
		"choice1":"Weather",
		"choice2":"Meteors",
		"choice3":"Metals",
		"choice4":"Earthquakes",
		"correct":"Weather"
	},
	{
		"id":"24",
		"question":"Oncology is the study of",
		"choice1":"Birds",
		"choice2":"Cancer",
		"choice3":"Mammals",
		"choice4":"Soil",
		"correct":"Cancer"
	},
	{
		"id":"25",
		"question":"Study of life in outer space is known as",
		"choice1":"Endobiology",
		"choice2":"Exobiology ",
		"choice3":"Enterobiology",
		"choice4":"Neobiology",
		"correct":"Exobiology "
	},
	{
		"id":"26",
		"question":"40. Ornithology is the",
		"choice1":"Study of bones",
		"choice2":"Study of birds",
		"choice3":"Study of smells",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"Study of birds"
	},
	{
		"id":"27",
		"question":"Who invented the Doctor â€™s thermometer?",
		"choice1":"Fahrenheit",
		"choice2":"Edison",
		"choice3":"Galileo",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"Fahrenheit"
	},
	{
		"id":"28",
		"question":"The velocity of light was first measured by",
		"choice1":"Einstein",
		"choice2":"Newton",
		"choice3":"Romer",
		"choice4":"Galileo",
		"correct":"Romer"
	},
	{
		"id":"29",
		"question":"Who proposed the chemical evolution of life?",
		"choice1":"Darwin",
		"choice2":"Lammarck",
		"choice3":"Oparin",
		"choice4":"Haechel",
		"correct":"Oparin "
	},
	{
		"id":"30",
		"question":"The telephone was invented by",
		"choice1":"John Logie Baird",
		"choice2":"Alexander Graham Bell",
		"choice3":"Thomas Elva Edison",
		"choice4":"James Watt",
		"correct":"Alexander Graham Bell"
	},
	{
		"id":"31",
		"question":"Who among the following evolved the concept of relationship between mass and energy?",
		"choice1":"Einstein",
		"choice2":"Planck",
		"choice3":"Dalton",
		"choice4":"Rutherford9",
		"correct":"Einstein"
	},
	{
		"id":"32",
		"question":"Robert Koch worked on",
		"choice1":"Tuberculosis",
		"choice2":"Cholera",
		"choice3":"Malaria",
		"choice4":"Diabetes",
		"correct":"Tuberculosis"
	},
	{
		"id":"33",
		"question":"Who discovered Uranus?",
		"choice1":"Herschel",                                
		"choice2":"Ganleo",
		"choice3":"Copernicus",                          
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"Herschel"
	},
	{
		"id":"34",
		"question":"Which rare element would you associate with Marie and Pierre Curie?",
		"choice1":"Platinum",
		"choice2":"Radium",
		"choice3":"Uranium",
		"choice4":"Gold",
		"correct":"Radium"
	},
	{
		"id":"35",
		"question":"The animal kingdom is formally classified into major groups known as",
		"choice1":"Orders",
		"choice2":"Families",
		"choice3":"Sub Phyla",
		"choice4":"Phyla",
		"correct":"Phyla"
	},
	{	"id":"36",
		"question":"The atom is made of",
		"choice1":"Positrons, Neutrons and Electrons",
		"choice2":"Neutrinos, Gamma Rays and Positrons",
		"choice3":"Protons and Quarks",
		"choice4":"Protons, Neutrons and Electrons",
		"correct":"Protons, Neutrons and Electrons"
	},
	{	"id":"37",
		"question":"Which gas evolves when charcoal is burnt?",
		"choice1":"Ozone",
		"choice2":"Nitrogen",
		"choice3":"Oxygen",
		"choice4":"Carbon Dioxide",
		"correct":"Carbon Dioxide"
	},
	{
		"id":"38",
		"question":"Who invented the miner's safety-lamp?",
		"choice1":"Thomas Alva Edison",
		"choice2":"Sir Frank Whittle",
		"choice3":"Alexander Graham Bell",
		"choice4":"Sir Humphrey Davy",
		"correct":"Sir Humphrey Davy"
	},
	{
		"id":"39",
		"question":"Who wrote the book The Origin of Species?",
		"choice1":"Louis Pasteur",
		"choice2":"Charles Darwin",
		"choice3":"Sir Alexander Fleming",
		"choice4":"Stephen Hawking",
		"correct":"Charles Darwin"
	},
	{
		"id":"40",
		"question":"Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
		"choice1":"Mercury",
		"choice2":"Earth",
		"choice3":"Mars",
		"choice4":"Jupiter",
		"correct":"Mars"
	},
	{
		"id":"41",
		"question":"How many planets are there in our solar system?",
		"choice1":"8",
		"choice2":"9",
		"choice3":"10",
		"choice4":"12",
		"correct":"9"
	},
	{
		"id":"42",
		"question":"The Earth is surrounded by an insulating blanket of gases which protects it from the light and heat of the Sun. This insulating layer is called the?",
		"choice1":"Biosphere",
		"choice2":"Atmosphere",
		"choice3":"Hydrosphere",
		"choice4":"Lithosphere",
		"correct":"Atmosphere"
	},
	{
		"id":"43",
		"question":"What is the name given to molten rocks erupted by a volcano?",
		"choice1":"Firestone",
		"choice2":"Lava",
		"choice3":"Crater",
		"choice4":"Geyser",
		"correct":"Lava"
	},
	{
		"id":"44",
		"question":"Enzymes and anti-bodies are mainly made of",
		"choice1":"Proteins",
		"choice2":"Fats",
		"choice3":"Vitamins",
		"choice4":"Carbohydrates",
		"correct":"Proteins"
	},
	{
		"id":"45",
		"question":"Ordinary table salt is sodium chloride. What is baking soda?",
		"choice1":"Potassium chloride",
		"choice2":"Potassium carbonate",
		"choice3":"Potassium hydroxide",
		"choice4":"Sodium bicarbonate",
		"correct":"Sodium bicarbonate"
	},
	{
		"id":"46",
		"question":"Ozone hole refers to",
		"choice1":"hole in ozone layer",
		"choice2":"decrease in the ozone layer in troposphere",
		"choice3":"decrease in thickness of ozone layer in stratosphere",
		"choice4":"increase in the thickness of ozone layer in troposphere",
		"correct":"decrease in thickness of ozone layer in stratosphere"
	},
	{
		"id":"47",
		"question":"Pollination is best defined as",
		"choice1":"transfer of pollen from anther to stigma",
		"choice2":"germination of pollen grains",
		"choice3":"growth of pollen tube in ovule",
		"choice4":"visiting flowers by insects",
		"correct":"transfer of pollen from anther to stigma"
	},
	{
		"id":"48",
		"question":"Plants receive their nutrients mainly from",
		"choice1":"chlorophyll",
		"choice2":"atmosphere",
		"choice3":"light",
		"choice4":"soil",
		"correct":"soil"
	},
	{
		"id":"49",
		"question":"Movement of cell against concentration gradient is called",
		"choice1":"osmosis",
		"choice2":"active transport",
		"choice3":"diffusion",
		"choice4":"passive transport",
		"correct":"active transport"
	},
	{
	"id":"50",
		"question":"Photosynthesis generally takes place in which parts of the plant?",
		"choice1":"Leaf and other chloroplast bearing parts",
		"choice2":"steam and leaf",
		"choice3":"Roots and chloroplast bearing parts",
		"choice4":"Bark and leaf",
		"correct":"Leaf and other chloroplast bearing parts"
	},
	{
		"id":"51",
		"question":"Plants synthesis protein from",
		"choice1":"starch",
		"choice2":"sugar",
		"choice3":"amino acids",
		"choice4":"fatty acids",
		"correct":"amino acids"
	},
	{
		"id":"52",
		"question":"Plants absorb dissolved nitrates from soil and convert them into",
		"choice1":"free nitrogen",
		"choice2":"urea",
		"choice3":"ammonia",
		"choice4":"proteins",
		"correct":"free nitrogen"
	},
	{
		"id":"53",
		"question":"One of the following is not a function of bones.",
		"choice1":"Place for muscle attachment",
		"choice2":"Protection of vital organs",
		"choice3":"Secretion of hormones for calcium regulation in blood and bones",
		"choice4":"Production of blood corpuscles",
		"correct":"Secretion of hormones for calcium regulation in blood and bones"
	},
	{
		"id":"54",
		"question":"Photo-oxidation is",
		"choice1":"photo respiration",
		"choice2":"photolysis",
		"choice3":"light and oxygen induced breakdown",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"All of the above"
	},
	{
		"id":"55",
		"question":"Plants absorb most part of water needed by them through their",
		"choice1":"embryonic zone",
		"choice2":"growing point",
		"choice3":"root hairs",
		"choice4":"zone of elongation",
		"correct":"root hairs"
	},
	{
		"id":"56",
		"question":"Most highly intelligent mammals are",
		"choice1":"whales",
		"choice2":"dolphins",
		"choice3":"elephants",
		"choice4":"kangaroos",
		"correct":"dolphins"
	},
	{
		"id":"57",
		"question":"Plant development is influenced by",
		"choice1":"quality of light only",
		"choice1":"quality and duration of light",
		"choice2":"Sequential",
		"choice3":"quality and quantity of light",
		"choice4":"quality, quantity and duration of light",
		"correct":"quality, quantity and duration of light"
	},
	{
		"id":"58",
		"question":"Prokaryotic cells lack",
		"choice1":"nucleolus",
		"choice2":"nuclear membrane",
		"choice3":"membrane bound by organelles",
		"choice4":"All of these",
		"correct":"All of these"
	},
	{
		"id":"59",
		"question":"Photosynthesis takes place faster in",
		"choice1":"yellow light",
		"choice2":"white light",
		"choice3":"red light",
		"choice4":"darkness",
		"correct":"white light"
	},
	{
		"id":"60",
		"question":"Nucleus, the genetic material containing rounded body in each cell, was first discovered in 1831 by",
		"choice1":"Robert Hooke",
		"choice2":"Robert Brown",
		"choice3":"Rudolf Virchow",
		"choice4":"Theodore Schwann",
		"correct":"Robert Brown"
	},
	{
		"id":"61",
		"question":"Primary phloem develops from",
		"choice1":"lateral meristem",
		"choice2":"protoderm",
		"choice3":"extrastelar cambium",
		"choice4":"provascular tissue",
		"correct":"provascular tissue"
	},
	{
		"id":"62",
		"question":"Other than spreading malaria, anopheles mosquitoes are also vectors of",
		"choice1":"dengue fever",
		"choice2":"filariasis",
		"choice3":"encephalitis",
		"choice4":"yellow fever",
		"correct":"filariasis"
	},
	{
		"id":"63",
		"question":"Pyorrhoea is a disease of the",
		"choice1":"nose",
		"choice2":"gums",
		"choice3":"heart",
		"choice4":"lungs",
		"correct":"gums"
	},
	{
		"id":"64",
		"question":"O2 released in the process of photosynthesis comes from",
		"choice1":"CO2",
		"choice2":"water",
		"choice3":"sugar",
		"choice4":"pyruvic acid",
		"correct":"water"
	},
	{
		"id":"65",
		"question":"Placenta is the structure formed",
		"choice1":"by the union of foetal and uterine tissue",
		"choice2":"by foetus only",
		"choice3":"by fusion of germ layers",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"by the union of foetal and uterine tissue"
	},
	{
		"id":"66",
		"question":"Plants hormone that induces cell division is",
		"choice1":"auxins",
		"choice2":"gibberellins",
		"choice3":"kinins",
		"choice4":"domins",
		"correct":"kinins"
	},
	{
		"id":"67",
		"question":"Phloem is a tissue found in",
		"choice1":"reproductive organs of animals",
		"choice2":"plants",
		"choice3":"insects",
		"choice4":"mammals",
		"correct":"plants"
	},
	{
		"id":"68",
		"question":"N2 content is kept constant in the biosphere due to",
		"choice1":"N2 fixation",
		"choice2":"industrial pollution",
		"choice3":"nitrogen cycle",
		"choice4":"absorption of N2",
		"correct":"nitrogen cycle"
	},
	{
		"id":"69",
		"question":"Out of proteins, lipids and carbohydrates present in a cell membrane, what is true?",
		"choice1":"Lipids are maximum",
		"choice2":"Carbohydrates are minimum",
		"choice3":"Carbohydrates are maximum",
		"choice4":"All three are in equal proportion",
		"correct":"Carbohydrates are minimum"
	},
	{
		"id":"70",
		"question":"Potato is a modified form (outgrowth) of",
		"choice1":"root",
		"choice2":"stem",
		"choice3":"fruit",
		"choice4":"leaf",
		"correct":"stem"
	},
	{
		"id":"71",
		"question":"Of the following taxonomic categories which is the most inclusive (i.e. is the highest in hierarchy)?",
		"choice1":"Order",
		"choice2":"Subspecies",
		"choice3":"Class",
		"choice4":"Genus",
		"correct":"Class"
	},
	{
		"id":"72",
		"question":"Prothrombin which helps in clotting of blood is released by",
		"choice1":"lymphocytes",
		"choice2":"erythrocytes",
		"choice3":"monocytes",
		"choice4":"blood platelets",
		"correct":"blood platelets"
	},
	{
		"id":"73",
		"question":"Myopia is connected with",
		"choice1":"ears",
		"choice2":"eyes",
		"choice3":"lungs",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"eyes"
	},
	{
		"id":"74",
		"question":"Most of the red, blue and purple colours of plants are due to a pigment called",
		"choice1":"anthocyanin",
		"choice2":"carotene",
		"choice3":"chlorophyll",
		"choice4":"xanthophylls",
		"correct":"anthocyanin"
	},
	{
		"id":"75",
		"question":"Plants developing in dry conditions are",
		"choice1":"xerophytes",
		"choice2":"mesophytes",
		"choice3":"ithophytes",
		"choice4":"hydrophytes",
		"correct":"xerophytes"
	},
	{
		"id":"76",
		"question":"Plants growing on sand are called as",
		"choice1":"chasmophytes",
		"choice2":"oxylophytes",
		"choice3":"lithophytes",
		"choice4":"psammophytes",
		"correct":"psammophytes"
	},
	{
		"id":"77",
		"question":"Our skin, when exposed to excess sunlight, becomes dark. This is because our skin pigments called",
		"choice1":"flavoxanthin",
		"choice2":"melanin",
		"choice3":"carotene",
		"choice4":"Xanthophyll",
		"correct":"melanin"
	},
	{
		"id":"78",
		"question":"Ramapithecus and Cro-Magnon man are considered",
		"choice1":"ancestors of modern man",
		"choice2":"ancestors of monkey",
		"choice3":"ancestors of lion",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"ancestors of modern man"
	},
	{
		"id":"79",
		"question":"Normal adult human male has",
		"choice1":"10 gram of haemoglobin/100 gram of blood",
		"choice2":"14 gram of haemoglobin/100 gram of blood",
		"choice3":"18 gram of haemoglobin/100 gram of blood",
		"choice4":"24 gram of haemoglobin/100 gram of blood",
		"correct":"14 gram of haemoglobin/100 gram of blood"
	},
	{
		"id":"80",
		"question":"Plants wilt due to excess of",
		"choice1":"transpiration",
		"choice2":"photosynthesis",
		"choice3":"absorption",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"transpiration"
	},
	{
		"id":"81",
		"question":"Monotremes are unique mammals because they",
		"choice1":"posses hair",
		"choice2":"give birth to live young",
		"choice3":"secret milk in a pouch",
		"choice4":"lay eggs",
		"correct":"lay eggs"
	},
	{
		"id":"82",
		"question":"Poison glands of snakes are homologous to",
		"choice1":"electric organs of fishes",
		"choice2":"stings of rays",
		"choice3":"sebaceous glands of mammals",
		"choice4":"salivary glands of vertebrates",
		"correct":"salivary glands of vertebrates"
	},
	{
		"id":"83",
		"question":"Plant bends towards the source of light on account of the movement of curvature known as",
		"choice1":"geotropism",
		"choice2":"thigmotropism",
		"choice3":"chemotropism",
		"choice4":"phototropism",
		"correct":"phototropism"
	},
	{
		"id":"84",
		"question":"Plant have ____ while animals lack it",
		"choice1":"starch",
		"choice2":"cellulose",
		"choice3":"protein",
		"choice4":"fat",
		"correct":"cellulose"
	},
	{
		"id":"85",
		"question":"Photosynthesis is a process",
		"choice1":"reductive and exergonic",
		"choice2":"reductive and catabolic",
		"choice3":"reductive, endergonic and catabolic",
		"choice4":"reductive, endergonic and anabolic",
		"correct":"reductive, endergonic and anabolic"
	},
	{
		"id":"86",
		"question":"On which of the following plants did Gregor Mendal perform his classical experiment?",
		"choice1":"Gram",
		"choice2":"Maize",
		"choice3":"Pea",
		"choice4":"Wheat",
		"correct":"Pea"
	},
	{
		"id":"87",
		"question":"Pigmentation of skin is due to",
		"choice1":"lymphocytes",
		"choice2":"monocytes",
		"choice3":"leucocytes",
		"choice4":"melanocytes",
		"correct":"melanocytes"
	},
	{
		"id":"88",
		"question":"Norepinephrine increases",
		"choice1":"respiration",
		"choice2":"urine production",
		"choice3":"saliva production",
		"choice4":"blood pressure",
		"correct":"blood pressure"
	},
	{	
		"id":"89",
		"question":"Night blindness is cause by lack of which vitamin?",
		"choice1":"Vitamin A",
		"choice2":"Vitamin B",
		"choice3":"Vitamin C",
		"choice4":"Vitamin D",
		"correct":"Vitamin A"
	},
	{	
		"id":"90",
		"question":"Monocot root differs from dicot root in having",
		"choice1":"open vascular bundles",
		"choice2":"scattered vascular bundles",
		"choice3":"well developed pith",
		"choice4":"radially arranged vascular bundles",
		"correct":"well developed pith"
	},
	{	
		"id":"91",
		"question":"Radioactivity is a phenomenon of the spontaneous emission of",
		"choice1":"protons (alpha particles)",
		"choice2":"electrons (beta particles)",
		"choice3":"gamma rays (short wave electromagnetic waves)",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"All of the above"
	},
	{	
		"id":"92",
		"question":"Organic Substances which, in very small amounts, control growth and development called",
		"choice1":"vitamins",
		"choice2":"hormones",
		"choice3":"enzymes",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"hormones"
	},
	{	
		"id":"93",
		"question":"Our major foods, fibres, spices, fruits and beverage crops are",
		"choice1":"flowering plants",
		"choice2":"gymnosperms plants",
		"choice3":"pteridophytes",
		"choice4":"bryophytes",
		"correct":"flowering plants"
	},
	{	
		"id":"94",
		"question":"Movements due to light are shown by",
		"choice1":"flowering plants",
		"choice2":"lower plants",
		"choice3":"all land plants",
		"choice4":"all the plants",
		"correct":"flowering plants"
	},
	{	
		"id":"95",
		"question":"Outer covering of virus made up of protein is",
		"choice1":"capsid",
		"choice2":"coat",
		"choice3":"virion",
		"choice4":"viriod",
		"correct":"capsid"
	},
	{	
		"id":"96",
		"question":"Radish is a",
		"choice1":"bulb",
		"choice2":"conn",
		"choice3":"modified root",
		"choice4":"tuber",
		"correct":"modified root"
	},
	{	
		"id":"97",
		"question":"Most abundant tissues of our body are",
		"choice1":"	muscular",
		"choice2":"connective",
		"choice3":"epithelial",
		"choice4":"nervous",
		"correct":"connective"
	},
	{	
		"id":"98",
		"question":"Mumps is a disease caused by",
		"choice1":"fungus",
		"choice2":"bacterium",
		"choice3":"virus",
		"choice4":"None of these",
		"correct":"virus"
	},
	{	
		"id":"99",
		"question":"Rain water helps to increase the ____ to some extent",
		"choice1":"phosphorous contents",
		"choice2":"nitrogen contents",
		"choice3":"calcium contents",
		"choice4":"potash contents",
		"correct":"calcium contents"
	}
	]
	
	